[Music]
after the lockdown people were faced
with uncertainty about health safety and
resuming normal life questions about
health insurance tele medicine and
accessing expert advice without stepping
out were common akiki Lombard addressed
these concerns through the IL take care
app
[Music]
putting Comprehensive Health insurance
at people's fingertips and empowering
them to take the first step toward a
healthier future to raise awareness a
campaign was designed to showcase the
apps USBS through testimonials engaging
bloggers and experts to address audience
questions
effectively Finance bloggers like Atul
Lancelot and harini talked about how to
choose the right health insurance for
yourself or your family in the new
normal Dr bloggers Dr Roshan and Dr
Amita talked about the importance of
tele medicine and health insurance in a
post lockdown World deeper in her real
talked about online health services and
how it has helped
her gjan in her real not only talked
about how to stay healthy in The New
Normal she also showcased the IL take
care app we use the multiplatform and
multic content forms approach to ensure
wide reach and to activate multiple
touch points 20 blog posts served as
credible source of information for
audiences creating SEO
impact 20 blogger videos worked as
anecdotal recommendations for ICI
Lombard social media sessions on Twitter
and Facebook were conducted to open a
two-way communication between branded
and TG blog Chatters copyrighted
amplification ation pattern which cross
promote content assets led to improved
reach how blog chatter created impact
for the brand video plus text
approach activating consumer
community no dull day in the
campaign campaign
impact reach 26 million
people impressions
67.8 million SEO impact 30% of blog
posts showed up on the first page of
Google search ensuring better reach and
engagement the campaign messaging was a
success as the final reach and
Impressions we clocked were more than
300% of the targeted numbers
[Music]